<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
  - SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2024 MyDash Contributors
  - SPDX-License-Identifier: AGPL-3.0-or-later
-->
<info xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	  xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://apps.nextcloud.com/schema/apps/info.xsd">
	<id>mydash</id>
	<name lang="en">MyDash</name>
	<name lang="nl">MyDash</name>
	<summary lang="en">Drag-and-drop dashboards with templates, tiles, and smart visibility</summary>
	<summary lang="nl">Drag-and-drop dashboards met templates, tegels en slimme zichtbaarheid</summary>
	<description lang="en"><![CDATA[MyDash supercharges the Nextcloud dashboard. Create personalized workspaces with drag-and-drop widgets, custom shortcut tiles, and smart visibility rules — then let admins roll out templates to entire teams.

**Key Features**

- **Drag-and-drop grid layout** — Position and resize widgets freely on a flexible grid
- **Multiple dashboards** — Create as many dashboards as you need and switch between them
- **Custom tiles** — Add shortcut cards with icons, colors, and links to your most-used tools
- **Admin templates** — Pre-configure dashboards and distribute them to user groups with one click
- **Permission levels** — Choose view-only, add-only, or full customization per template
- **Conditional visibility** — Show or hide widgets based on group membership, time of day, or date
- **Widget styling** — Customize colors, borders, and titles for each individual widget
- **Compulsory widgets** — Admins can pin important widgets that users cannot remove
- **Full Nextcloud compatibility** — Works with every existing Nextcloud dashboard widget out of the box

Perfect for organizations that want consistent, curated dashboards for their teams while still giving users freedom to personalize.

Free and open source under the AGPL license.
    ]]></description>
	<description lang="nl"><![CDATA[MyDash geeft het Nextcloud-dashboard superkrachten. Maak persoonlijke werkruimtes met drag-and-drop widgets, eigen snelkoppelingstegels en slimme zichtbaarheidsregels — en laat beheerders templates uitrollen naar hele teams.

**Belangrijkste functies**

- **Drag-and-drop grid layout** — Positioneer en schaal widgets vrij op een flexibel raster
- **Meerdere dashboards** — Maak zoveel dashboards als je nodig hebt en wissel ertussen
- **Eigen tegels** — Voeg snelkoppelingskaarten toe met iconen, kleuren en links naar je meestgebruikte tools
- **Beheerdertemplates** — Configureer dashboards vooraf en distribueer ze met een klik naar gebruikersgroepen
- **Rechtenniveaus** — Kies tussen alleen bekijken, toevoegen, of volledige aanpassing per template
- **Conditionele zichtbaarheid** — Toon of verberg widgets op basis van groepslidmaatschap, tijdstip of datum
- **Widget-styling** — Pas kleuren, randen en titels aan voor elke individuele widget
- **Verplichte widgets** — Beheerders kunnen belangrijke widgets vastzetten die gebruikers niet kunnen verwijderen
- **Volledige Nextcloud-compatibiliteit** — Werkt direct met elke bestaande Nextcloud dashboard-widget

Ideaal voor organisaties die consistente, samengestelde dashboards willen voor hun teams, terwijl gebruikers de vrijheid houden om te personaliseren.

Vrij en open source onder de AGPL-licentie.
    ]]></description>
	<version>1.0.1-unstable.1</version>
	<licence>agpl</licence>
	<author mail="info@conduction.nl" homepage="https://www.conduction.nl/">Conduction</author>
	<namespace>MyDash</namespace>
	<documentation>
		<user>https://github.com/ConductionNL/mydash</user>
		<admin>https://github.com/ConductionNL/mydash</admin>
		<developer>https://github.com/ConductionNL/mydash</developer>
	</documentation>
	<category>customization</category>
	<category>organization</category>
	<category>dashboard</category>
	<website>https://github.com/ConductionNL/mydash</website>
	<discussion>https://github.com/ConductionNL/mydash/discussions</discussion>
	<bugs>https://github.com/ConductionNL/mydash/issues</bugs>
	<repository>https://github.com/ConductionNL/mydash</repository>

	<screenshot>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ConductionNL/mydash/main/img/app-store.svg</screenshot>
	<screenshot>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ConductionNL/mydash/main/img/screenshot.png</screenshot>

	<dependencies>
		<php min-version="8.1"/>
		<nextcloud min-version="28" max-version="33"/>
	</dependencies>

	<settings>
		<admin>OCA\MyDash\Settings\MyDashAdmin</admin>
		<admin-section>OCA\MyDash\Settings\MyDashAdminSection</admin-section>
	</settings>

	<navigations>
		<navigation>
			<name>MyDash</name>
			<route>mydash.page.index</route>
			<icon>app.svg</icon>
			<order>-5</order>
		</navigation>
	</navigations>
</info>
